loopd.com 2009-06-27

# www.loopd.com - Legal - Privacy Policy

The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and sub-domains of [www.sponsorhouse.com](http://www.sponsorhouse.com/) and domains and subdomains that may be utilizing the services or modules of SponsorHouse.com. Please note that this Policy applies only to sites maintained by SponsorHouse.com and not to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link. In addition, this Policy applies only to information collected by SponsorHouse online, not offline. By visiting our websites you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our services.

SponsorHouse is committed to providing a safe and secure website for people of all ages. We are dedicated to safeguarding all personal information collected online. Because children may visit this website, we employ special measures to help children protect their privacy while online. We do not ask children to disclose more personal information than is necessary for them to participate in a particular activity, and we take steps to prevent children from posting contact information.  We urge children to check with their parents before entering information on any website and we urge parents to discuss with their kids restrictions regarding the online release of personal information to anyone they don’t know.

For purposes of this Privacy Policy (“Policy” or “Privacy Policy”), the terms “we,” “us,” “our” and 

Loopd.com and “SponsorHouse.com” refer to SponsorHouse, Inc. d.b.a Loop’d Network, a Delaware corporation, and “you” and “your” refers to you, as a user of the SponsorHouse.com service. The Privacy Policy below governs your SponsorHouse.com account and any information you provide on this site.

 **A.  Overview:**In order to operate the SponsorHouse.com service and to provide our services, including, but not limited to, matching Participants (more fully described below) with sponsors, sponsors with Participants, Participants with friends, fans, promoters, and businesses we must ask you to provide some information about yourself. SponsorHouse.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We want to provide a safe, secure user experience. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private, and is used only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected or submitted on the SponsorHouse.com website. We will not sell or rent your nonpublic personal information to third parties except as set forth in Part E below. As described in more detail in Part E below, there are limited circumstances in which some of your nonpublic personal information will be shared with third parties, so it is important for you to review this Privacy Policy. “Participants” shall include, but not be limited to, athletes, drivers, gamers, musicians, models, actors, entertainers and celebrities.  
By using the SponsorHouse.com service, you expressly consent to our collection and use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. If you object to your nonpublic personal information being transferred or used as described in this Privacy Policy, please do not register for the SponsorHouse.com service. This Policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the SponsorHouse.com service or as we incorporate suggestions from our account holders. Any material changes will be effective immediately. The amended Privacy Policy will always be posted on our website. 

 **B.  What information of yours we collect:**

 _CHILDREN UNDER 13_

: Generally, we limit our collection of information from children to what is known as non-personally identifiable information (screen names, gender, state). This information is collected so kids can participate in activities (chat with athletes and celebrities, post messages) without giving unnecessary personal information. From time to time, however, we may request limited personally identifiable information (kid's email address and/or email address of parent or third party), as explained below, in order to conduct or offer other online activities (matching Participants with sponsors, sponsors with Participants, Participants with friends, fans, promoters, and businesses). SponsorHouse does not condition a kid’s participation in any of our online activities on the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. As explained below, we also collect from parents additional types of information (credit card and billing information) when they purchase memberships or products and offerings at our website.  
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:  
* Information we may receive when you sign up to use our service, communicate with other users, communicate with us, enter into a contest, apply for or offer sponsorship, rate or rank photos and content, or purchase or sell a product or service through a SponsorHouse.com, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, type of computer and similar information.

* Information we may receive from forms and surveys on our site that we request you to complete in an effort to deliver to you the best possible site experience, such as information on your interests, your gender, your age, your likes and dislikes regarding the site and its content and other similar information.  
* In addition, we may receive information about you from other sources (such as service providers or third party sites linked to our site) for tracking and advertising purposes.  
* When a child under thirteen participates in an activity that requires the collection, retention, and use of personal information, we will also ask for a parent's e-mail address so that we can notify the parent that we have received personal information from their child. We also may ask for parental verification by accepting and verifying a valid credit card number. We do not knowingly collect names and e-mail addresses from children under thirteen without notifying the parent via e-mail and giving the parent the option to remove their child's e-mail address and other information from our database.

 **C.  How your information is used:** We may use nonpublic personal information we collect about you in the following ways:  
* To provide the services you are requesting, route your order or inquiry entered on SponsorHouse.com to the applicable sponsor or website, respond to your requests, customize your experience on the SponsorHouse.com website and contact you regarding your account.  
* In the aggregate, to help us determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall experience for you.  
* To measure and improve our customer service, and to investigate potential fraud and violations of this Policy or any other agreement we have with you. We may, over time, delete correspondence records with you if permitted by law.  
* We use a software technology called “cookies.” Cookies are small text files that we place in visitors’ computer browsers to store their preferences. Cookies themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information. We do use session cookies to ensure that visitors under the age of 13 provide a parental email address to assist with our compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. We do use cookies to determine how many visitors we have and how often they visit various sections of our site. Once you log out or close your browser, session cookies expire and no longer have any effect.  
* To notify you if you are a winner and to award you prizes that you may have won. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.  
* In the case of children using our website and services, we use parents' e-mail addresses to notify them when we have received personal information such as e-mail addresses from their children and to give parents the option to remove their child's name from our lists. Parents have the option to agree to the collection and use of their child's information without consenting to the disclosure of the information to third parties.  
If you give us specific permission, we may use your nonpublic personal information to:  
* Make you aware of additional products and services that may be of interest to you or to contact you regarding site changes.   You can choose whether to receive some, all or none of these communications.  
* Post your resume and profile in our searchable database as you request, thereby making it available to search queries by other users of our site.  
* If you have any questions on the use or disclosure of your personal information, please feel free to send us your request in writing at the mailing address provided below. Please allow up to thirty days for our response.

 **D.  Parental Review of Information**

Parents, please send a letter or postcard to our SponsorHouse Privacy Manager at the mailing address provided below if you would like to do any of the following:

  * access personally identifiable information that the SponsorHouse website has collected online from your child,
  * correct factual errors in such information,
  * request to have this information deleted, or
  * request that we no longer collect or maintain such information.

Please be sure to include your e-mail address and a telephone number where we can reach you. To protect your child's privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the personal information that we collect and maintain about your child.

 **E.  With whom your information may be shared**

We share your nonpublic personal information:  
* With our service providers that perform functions on our behalf, such as, hosting our website servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, providing customer service and providing messaging services such as electronic mail and instant messaging. These service providers may have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions. Although we require such entities to support our Privacy Policy, and to comply with applicable federal and state laws, we do not have any direct control over such entities nor do we guarantee or warrant their use and handling of your personal information.  
* With subsidiaries and affiliates, as permitted by law, for legal purposes, for the protection of our site, for the protection of SponsorHouse.com (or any of its partners, employees, third party vendors, independent contractors or affiliates) and/or for the protection of other users of our site. Specifically, we reserve the right to disclose personal information as allowed by law or share your personal information with third parties if required by law to do so, or if we believe such action is necessary to either: (a) conform with the requirements of law enforcement or government agencies in response to subpoenas, court orders, federal/state audits or similar circumstances, or as otherwise required by law, (b) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our site, or other users of our site, or (c) investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person.

* With respect to resumes and profiles that you instruct us to make available, with other users of our site who have paid for access to our resume and profile database.  
* Through the SponsorHouse.com website, you have the ability to indicate your interest in being contacted by sponsors, Participants or other members. Your nonpublic personal information will be used to match you with sponsors, Participants and other members. Once we match you with sponsors, Participants and other members, we will indicate these to you and will give you the opportunity to receive information from them. If you approve, we will share your personal information with such sponsors, Participants and other members. Sponsors are governed by their own privacy statements and policies, and SponsorHouse.com is not responsible for their operations, including but not limited to their information practices.  
PARENTS: You can request that you child not receive communications from sponsors, Participants or other parties. You can make your request by sending a letter or postcard to our SponsorHouse Privacy Manager at the mailing address provided below.  
* In the aggregate with our partners so that they too may understand how SponsorHouse.com visitors use our site and so they may create a better overall experience for you.  
* If SponsorHouse, Inc. (or substantially all of our assets) is acquired, your information would be transferred along with the other business assets as permitted by law. We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties as permitted by law.   
* PARENTS: We will not use or transfer personally identifiable information in ways that are materially different from the ones described above without also providing parental notification of such practices and obtaining consent for any materially different uses.

 **F.  Your choices regarding the collection, use and distribution of your information:**

Your SponsorHouse.com account preferences provides you with the ability to opt-in or opt-out of communications from SponsorHouse.com, sponsors, Participants and other parties. If you choose to receive these types of communications at the time of registration, but later decide you no longer want to receive them, simply log in to your account and edit your account preferences or by sending an email to [privacy@sponsorhouse.com](mailto:privacy@sponsorhouse.com). You may continue to receive email communications from SponsorHouse.com, our sponsors, Participants or other members for up to ten business days from the time we receive your unsubscribe request. Please note that SponsorHouse.com can only control its own mailing list and policies. Third party advertisers that maintain their own mailing lists may send communications that advertise our services, and you may need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving their email communications. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies. However, doing this will hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on our site. SponsorHouse.com has an area on the site where you can submit feedback. Any feedback that is submitted through this area becomes the property of SponsorHouse.com. We may use this feedback, such as success stories, for marketing purposes, or to contact you for further feedback on the site.  
PARENTS: You can request that you child not receive communications from sponsors, Participants or other parties. You can make your request by sending a letter or postcard to our SponsorHouse Privacy Manager at the mailing address provided below.

 **G.  Security procedures:** The security of your personal information is very important at SponsorHouse.com and we take a number of steps to safeguard it and protect the loss, and misuse of the information under our control. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures in an effort to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.  
You may remove your information from our searchable database at any time. We are not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of information in these instances, or for the use or privacy of resumes by any of such parties while resumes are in the database.  
When you submit payment information online for your membership, online order, or SponsorHouse.com fees, your personal details and credit card information are encrypted using industry-standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology before being sent over the Internet. Although we cannot guarantee encryption or the privacy of your personal details and credit card information, SSL makes it difficult for your information to be stolen or intercepted while being transferred. Our credit card transactions are maintained by a company called Authorize.net. All information sent to Authorize.net is encrypted, which will protect it against disclosure to third parties. When a sponsor receives notification of your order, it is kept encrypted until they’re ready to process it. For further information about Authorize.net’s privacy and security practices, please [Click Here](http://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/).

 **H.  Correcting inaccuracies in your information:**

SponsorHouse.com allows you to change or correct your personal information at any time. To do so, simply log into your account, go to your account profile, and you will find options for editing the information you have submitted. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about SponsorHouse.com’s privacy commitment, please feel free to email us at [privacy@sponsorhouse.com](mailto:privacy@sponsorhouse.com) to contact one of our representatives.  
PARENTS: You can request any corrections to your child’s account by sending a letter or postcard to our SponsorHouse Privacy Manager at the mailing address provided below.

 **I.  Links to Other Sites:  
**  
Please note, this Privacy Policy applies to all information that you provide to SponsorHouse.com only. The SponsorHouse.com website may include links to third party websites. SponsorHouse.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of or the content contained in other websites. When you use a link to go from our site to another website, or are otherwise directed or redirected to another website, this Privacy Policy no longer applies. Your browsing and activity on such third party websites are subject to their own respective privacy policies, if any, which may differ from that of SponsorHouse.com. Users submitting information to or through these third party websites should review the privacy statement and policy of these sites before providing them with personally identifiable financial information. The SponsorHouse.com website contains shops of Sponsors that sell products to members that they sponsor (“Sponsor Shops”). When you purchase a product from a sponsor through its Sponsor Shop, the information you provide with your transaction will be collected by both the sponsor and us. Any information you provide on a co-branded registration page, such as that of a SponsorHouse.com and other company-sponsored contest, will be collected by both us and the other party co-sponsoring the contest. Accordingly, the personal information you enter on Sponsor Shops and on co-branded pages is subject to both this Policy, with respect to SponsorHouse.com, and to the privacy policy of the sponsor or the other party co-sponsoring the contest, with respect to their use, and SponsorHouse.com is not responsible for any use of your personal information by the sponsor or the other party co-sponsoring the contest, as the case may be.

 **J.  Contact Us** If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our privacy policy and/or practices, please contact us at the following e-mail address, mailing address and telephone number:  
Email: [privacy@sponsorhouse.com](mailto:privacy@sponsorhouse.com)  
Mailing Address: SponsorHouse, Inc.

3560 Dunhill Street   
San Diego , CA 92121  
K. Your California Privacy Rights  
Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to 

_[privacy@sponsorhouse.com](mailto:privacy@sponsorhouse.com)_

 or write us:   SponsorHouse, Inc. Attn: Privacy Department3560 Dunhill Street  
San Diego , CA 92121

 **L.  Updates & Effective Date**

From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.

 **This Privacy Policy was last updated on October 1, 2006.**
